Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1475; 1 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1476; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Stern: Sani Lecture, 9 Mar 2009; cuid1477; 3 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - SHARP: Lecture Series: United States, 24 Nov 2008; cuid1478; 2 MiniDV (Box 80)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge: Inernational Relations, 4 Mar 2009; cuid1479; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Restored Financial Stability, 6 Mar 2009; cuid1480; 11 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - UVL 2009, 26 Feb 2009; cuid1481; 5 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1482; 4 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - NCDP Session 3: Afternoon Sessions, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1483; 4 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - New Multilateralism: Gordon M. Brown, 25 Mar 2009; cuid1484; 6 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Fales: Food and Celebration: A Long History, 5 Mar 2009; cuid1485; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Tamiment Conference: Academic Freedom, 3 Apr 2009; cuid1486; 8 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Michael Bllomberg and Non-Profits, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1487; 4 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - NYU Alumni and Friends, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1488; 5 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Courant: Jack Schwartz Memorial, 26 Mar 2009; cuid1489; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1490; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - GPH: Health in Africa, 16 Apr 2009; cuid1491; 2 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Courant Spring Lecture, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1492; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1493; 1 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1494; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - The 2009 Zuckerman Forum, 21 Apr 2009; cuid1495; 2 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - Fales Library: Annual Fales Lecture, 14 Apr 2009; cuid1496; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Media Talk with David Carr and Tina Brown, 25 Feb 2009; cuid1497; 5 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Scholars and Artists: George Stoney, 29 Apri 2009; cuid1498; 5 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Aramark: Opera Performance, 26 Apr 2009; cuid1499; 5 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Reynolds Social Entrepreneurial, 30 Apr 2009; cuid1500; 1 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - Obama's 100 Days, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1501; 8 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - National Public Policy Forum, 18 Apr 2009; cuid1502; 1 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Progress Review and Report, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1503; 2 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Shared Care Integrated, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1504; 2 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Depression Identification, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1505; 2 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Period 3 and Beyond, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1506; 2 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting: A Shared Vision for a Sustainable Region, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1507; 1 DVD-R (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Ninth Annual Cal Ramsey, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1508; 6 DVCAM (Box 79)
  - CAS: From Slavery to Freedom, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1509; 5 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Scholars and Artists, 30 Sep 2008; cuid1510; 4 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Coles Science Salon, 1 Oct 2008; cuid1511; 2 DVD-R (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1512; 5 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - CAS From Slavery to Freedom, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1513; 5 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - What's Next? The Global Financial Crisis, 20 Oct 2008; cuid1514; 4 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Arthur Miller, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1515; 4 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Crossing the Line, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1516; 2 MiniDV (Box 80)
  - Emerging and Disappering Immigrant, 16 Oct 2008; cuid1517; 1 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Global Public Health: Rethinking HIV, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1518; 1 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - President of Albania, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1519; 1 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Conscious Capitalism, 8 Oct 2008; cuid1520; 2 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - New Israel Fund, undated; cuid1521; 2 DVD-R (Box 80)
  - Rudin CTR: Making the Connection, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1522; 6 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Moving the Needle: Improving Collaboration, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1523; 2 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Depression Treatment, 25 Oct 2009; cuid1524; 2 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - Stern CFR Panel #1, 11 Nov 2008; cuid1525; 3 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - King David Gala, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1526; 6 DVCAM (Box 80)
  - SCPS Podcast: The Emergency Economic, 29 Oct 2008; cuid1527; 0 DVD-R (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership Powerpoint, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1528; 0 CD-ROM (Box 80)
  - Rudin Conference "Closing the Gap", 4 Jun 2014; cuid1529; 6 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - NCRW National Council for Research on Women, 6 Jun 2006; cuid1530; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Steinhardt Reading Recovery, 4 Jun 2008; cuid1531; 1 DVD-R (Box 81)
  - SMPTE-NY Meeting "File Exchange", 4 Jun 2008; cuid1532; 3 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - National Presidential Caucus: 2012 Primary, 24 Jun 2008; cuid1533; 5 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1534; 6 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1535; 16 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1536; 20 DVD-R (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute, 9 Jul 2008; cuid1537; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute Day Two, 10 Jul 2008; cuid1538; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Keynote, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1539; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 1 "Rewriting the Bible", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1540; 2 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 2 "The Dead Sea Sect", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1541; 2 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 3 "The Scrolls and Second Temple Judaism", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1542; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 4 "Judean Desert Texts", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1543; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Public Affairs Spotlight Shoot: Raw Footage, Penny Halkitis, Ann Morning, and Rough Cut, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1544; 4 VHS (Box 81)
  - Neil Postman: Raw Footage and Select Segments, undated; cuid1545; 3 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: LGBT Issues, undated; cuid1546; 4 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Washington Square News, undated; cuid1547; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: WNYU, undated; cuid1548; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Career Services, undated; cuid1549; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - OISS, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1550; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - OISS 1: American Idioms Seminar, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1551; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - OISS 2: Mixed Drinks American, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1552; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Interview with University Archivist Nancy Cricco, undated; cuid1553; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Clinton on Campus: Registration Campaign, 24 Apr 2002; cuid1554; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Conversations with Jie Tao, 15 Oct 1997; cuid1555; 1 DAT (Box 81)
  - New York University in London, 28 Nov 2001; cuid1556; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Fall 2002, 1 Oct 2002; cuid1557; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - Dogeaters: From Novel to the Stage, 30 Jan 2001; cuid1558; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: Skirball, 21 Aug 2008; cuid1559; 5 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1560; 4 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1561; 8 DVD-R (Box 81)
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sept 2008; cuid1562; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Simon Peres, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1563; 3 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Martha Graham Panels, 18 Sep 2008; cuid1564; 4 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Fales A.I.R. Gallery, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1565; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Financial Access Initiative: Program Feed, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1566; 1 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - Wagner Financial Access Initiative Event, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1567; 2 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - A Discussion with UK Foreign Secretary, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1568; 2 DVCAM (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Key Learning and Summary of Day 1, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1569; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Strategies for Sustaining, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1570; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Self Managment Team, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1571; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Progress Review, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1572; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Depression Care Workflow, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1573; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Primary Care Benefit, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1574; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Understanding the Importance, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1575; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Advanced Self Management, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1576; 1 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sep 2008; cuid1577; 2 MiniDV (Box 81)
  - 50th Anniversary of Brown vs. Board of Education lecture/panel, 17 May 2004; cuid1578; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 79)
    Barcode: 31142042272966
  - Stern Barcelona 2009: Global Alumni, 12 Jun 2009; cuid1579; 2 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - SCPS: McGhee "Online Interviews", 21 Jan 2009; cuid1580; 7 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies (CAS): Writing, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1581; 13 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Congressional Oversight Hearing, 28 May 2009; cuid1582; 3 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Fales Food Series: "NY Farm Connections", 4 Apr 2009; cuid1583; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Bankruptcy and the Financial Crisis, 30 Jun 2009; cuid1584; 6 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Reading Recovery Program Graduation, 5 Jun 2009; cuid1585; 2 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Reality Show, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1586; 5 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - NYU Portraits: Voices of a People, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1587; 5 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - College of Arts and Science Deans Lecture, 17 Sep 2009; cuid1588; 4 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1589; 3 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1590; 2 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1591; 3 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Constitution Day, 14 Sep 2009; cuid1592; 2 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1593; 14 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1594; 8 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Development Research Institute (DRI): What Would the Poor Say? Debateds in Aid Evaluations, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1595; 4 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - The Children of Buroughs: New York Archives, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1596; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - The Unbearables, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1597; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Drug-Resistant TB and HIV/AIDS in Southern Africa: Human Rights, Evidence, and the Public Good, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1598; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1599; 2 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1600; 1 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1601; 2 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1602; 4 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Music and Performing Arts Professions: Meeting on Disproportionality in Special Education, 9 Cct 2009; cuid1603; 5 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Student Health Center: H1N1 Forum, 14 Oct 2009; cuid1604; 2 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Creative Writing Program: Dance Program, 14 Dec 2008; cuid1605; 3 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Alumni Weekend: Happy Hour and Raffle, 3 Oct 2009; cuid1606; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Billy Collins Reading, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1607; 2 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - CAS Freshman Convocation, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1608; 3 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1609; 2 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1610; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Nursing Workshop, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1611; 2 DVD-R (Box 86)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Seth Goldman President and TeaEO of Honest Tea, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1612; 1 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Remarque Lecture: Tony Judt, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1613; 4 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - E.L. Doctorow Reader from "Homer and Langley", 22 Oct 2009; cuid1614; 3 DVCAM (Box 86)
  - Everything You Wanted to Know (and Didn't) About Film Festivals, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1615; 2 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1616; 1 DVD-R (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1617; 1 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Peter Orszag, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1618; 1 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Annual Leon Levy Lecture, 5 Nov 2009; cuid1619; 2 MiniDV (Box 87)
  - Medical Education Matters: A Theory Building Conference, 11 Nov 2009; cuid1620; 6 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Philip Kitcher, 16 Nov 2009; cuid1621; 2 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Courant Institute Alumni Presentation, 13 Nov 2009; cuid1622; 1 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - MLK Keynote Event: Howard Zinn, 21 Jan 2010; cuid1623; 3 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - "You are Cordially Invited": the Art and Influence of Robert Blanchon, 2010 Jan 26; cuid1624; 3 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Columbian Consulate Webcasts, 2010 Aug 8; cuid1625; 5 DVD-R (Box 87)
  - NYU Schack Institute of Real Estate Press, 2010 Jan 10; cuid1626; 4 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - National College Depression Partnership, 2000 Jan 15; cuid1627; 24 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - 11th Annual Irving H. Jurow Lecture, 2010 Feb 2; cuid1628; 3 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Fales Food Series: Italian Food in New York, 2010 Feb 3; cuid1629; 1 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - David Wonjnarowicz Photographer, 2010 Feb 4; cuid1630; 3 DVCAM (Box 87)
  - Humanities: Thinking Through Violence, 2010 Feb 9; cuid1631; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1632; 2 MiniDV (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1633; 1 DVD-R (Box 88)
  - Will Wright, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1634; 3 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - SCPS Schack Online Interviews, 2010 Jan 21; cuid1635; 6 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - CGA Public Events Series, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1636; 1 MiniDV (Box 88)
  - SCPS Podcast: Bjorn Hanson, 2010 Feb 22; cuid1637; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Schack Panel "Real Estate: A Local Business", 2010 Feb 23; cuid1638; 4 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Chris Jordan, 2010 Feb 23; cuid1639; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Ultraviolet Live, 2010 Feb 25; cuid1640; 5 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Google versus Apple: Who Will Win?, 2010 Mar 2; cuid1641; 4 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Mabou Mines Opening Night Reception, 2010 Mar 4; cuid1642; 2 DVD-R (Box 88)
  - Remappings: Asia/Pacific/America, 2010 Mar 5; cuid1643; 12 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Steinhardt Symphony Orchestra, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1644; 5 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Fales: Through Other Lenses, 2010 Mar 9; cuid1645; 3 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Hartford Institute: voice over recording, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1646; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 2010 Mar 18; cuid1647; 3 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Annual Fales Lecture, 2010 Mar 11; cuid1648; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - GME Program Director' Retreat Resident, 2010 Mar 22; cuid1649; 9 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Nursing Conference: Innovative Applications, 2010 Mar 19; cuid1650; 6 DVD-R (Box 88)
  - Fales Food Series: Food Media in New Media, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1651; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - UN: Bill Clinton Speaks about Haiti, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1652; 3 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Social Entrpreneruship in the 21st Century, 2010 Apr 1; cuid1653; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Vitamin A Deficiencies and Global Public Health, 2010 Mar 30; cuid1654; 1 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Stern School of Business, Social Impacting, 2010 Apr 5; cuid1655; 3 DVCAM (Box 88)
  - Ashok Sani Lecture: Mark K. Shriver, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1656; 2 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Unigo.com Wall Street Journal Panel, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1657; 4 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - University Professorship Lecture, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1658; 2 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Global Public Health: Mexico, 2010 Apr 9; cuid1659; 2 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Teaching with Technology, 2010 Apr 16; cuid1660; 3 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - New York University's Frederic Ewen, cuid1661; 3 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - SCPS Schack Career Fair, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1662; 3 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1663; 1 MiniDV (Box 89)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Anthony Romero, 2010 Apr 27; cuid1664; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Stern International Studies Program: ISP, 2010 Apr 30; cuid1665; 3 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Africa House: The Rule of Law and Business in Africa, 2010 May 3; cuid1666; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Courant Lecture: Alfio Quarteroni, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1667; 1 MiniDV (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Me in a Book, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1668; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - International Public Policy Forum, 2010 Apr 17; cuid1669; 6 DVD-R (Box 89)
  - Global Health Capstone Presentations, 2010 May 7; cuid1670; 3 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Courant Institute of Mathmatical Science Lecture, 2010 May 8; cuid1671; 6 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - The Mysteries and Marvels of Memory, 2010 Mar 27; cuid1672; 11 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - SCPS Presentation: Naomi Zigler, 2010 Apr 14; cuid1673; 1 MiniDV (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Feed Your Pet Right, 2010 May 27; cuid1674; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1675; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1676; 3 MiniDV (Box 85)
  - Secret Gardens: Powerful Plots in Surprising Places, 2010 Jun 17; cuid1677; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - NYU Libraries All Staff Meeting, 2010 Jun 21; cuid1678; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2010 Jun 25; cuid1679; 1 DVCAM (Box 89)
  - BARD High School Early College, 2010 Jun 24; cuid1680; 1 DVD-R (Box 89)
  - MetroCenter's 2010 Technical Assistance, 2010 Jul 9; cuid1681; 6 DVD-R (Box 89)
  - Presidential Welcome and Reality Show at Radio City, 2010 Aug 3 (Box 89)
  - Institute of Art and Civic Dialogue: Anna Deavere Smith, 2010 Oct 16; cuid1682; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1683; 2 DVD-R (Box 90)
  - Fales: Mary Ellen Solt Reading, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1684; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Interactive Arts Performance Series: Ear to the Earth, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1685; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Derek Jeter Podcast, 2010 Oct 28; cuid1686; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Amartya Sen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1687; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Fales Food Series: Back into the Kitchen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1688; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - George Stoney Tribute, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1689; 2 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Casa Italiano Anniversary, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1690; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture: Vladimir Vapnik, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1691; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Silver School of Social Work: 50th Anniversary, 2010 Nov 11; cuid1692; 4 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Tamiment Library: Philip Agee, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1693; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Pedagogy and Theatre of the Oppressed, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1694; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Commonweal Magazine Conversations, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1695; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Parents Day Simulcast, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1696; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - DNP Leadership Class Lecture, 2010 Nov 21; cuid1697; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Martin Fischer, 2010 Nov 29; cuid1698; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Jacob J. Javits Visiting Professorship, 2010 Dec 7; cuid1699; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - The Women's Conference, 2010 Oct 26; cuid1700; 2 DVD-R (Box 90)
  - A Conversation with Gordon Brown, MP, 2010 Dec 14; cuid1701; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - New Trustee Induction Ceremony, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1702; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - The Future of Nursing with Kristie Gebbie, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1703; 1 MiniDV (Box 90)
  - Courant: 75th Anniversary Holiday Lecture, 2010 Dec 16; cuid1704; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - An Evening with Senators Tom Daschle and Trent Lott, 2011 Feb 2; cuid1705; 3 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - America at a Crossroads: The dayton Accords, 2011 Feb 9; cuid1706; 8 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - Sheikh Mohamad bin Zayed Scholars Program, 2011 Feb 5; cuid1707; 1 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - A/P/A: Midnight on the Mavi Marmara, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1708; 1 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - Third Annual Global South Asia Conference, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1709; 1 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - Stern: Social Impacting Corporate Social, 2011 Mar 21; cuid1710; 3 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - SCPS: McGhee Egyptian Panel, 2011 Mar 22; cuid1711; 4 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - Reynold Speaker Series: Food Panel, 2011 Mar 23; cuid1712; 3 DVCAM (Box 91)
  - PLACEMARKER BOX 92, cuid1713 (Box 92)
  - Starworks Foundation Showcase with Jonathan Safran Foer and Matthea Harvey, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1714; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Fales: What's the Matter With Mass Produced?, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1715; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Fales: Visual Aids, What Comes Next?, 2011 Apr 20; cuid1716; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - NYU's Inaugural Distinguished Global leader Residence, 2011 Apr 4; cuid1717; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Courant Lecture: The Search for Randomness, 2011 Apr 7; cuid1718; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Presidents Service Awards, 2011 Apr 27; cuid1719; 4 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Wagner: Gordon Brown at Stern, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1720; 2 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Stern: Entrepreneur Competition Awards Final Pitch and Ceremony, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1721; 6 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - UDAR: Alumni Luncehon University Development and Alumni Relations, 2011 Apr 6; cuid1722; 4 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Courant 75th Anniversary Celebration, 2011 May 6; cuid1723; 9 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Business and White Collar Crime, 2011 Apr 25; cuid1724; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge Conference: Designing Mobility for Democracy: The Role of Cities, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1725; 6 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - NYU Trustee's Pre Commencement Dinner, 2011 May 17; cuid1726; 6 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Courant Summer Conference "Games for Change", 2011 Jun 20; cuid1727; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2011 Jun 24; cuid1728; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Stern Lunchtime Leadership Speaker Series, 2011 May 26; cuid1729; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Stern ISP: Final Presentation Competition, 2011 May 6; cuid1730; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Speakers on the Square: Mossette Broderick American Guilded Age, 2011 Jun 13; cuid1731; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Metro Centeres Technical Assistance Center of Disproportionality, 2011 Jul 6; cuid1732; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - SCPS Media Talk Magazines:The New Conversations, 2011 Jun 14; cuid1733; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Learning Leaders: Real Superheroes of NYC Public Schools, 2011 May 11; cuid1734; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Trends in Literary Translation, 2011 Apr 16; cuid1735; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Stern Entreprenuer Competition Awards, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1736; 3 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Fales: From Here to Harvesting, 2011 Jun 9; cuid1737; 1 DVCAM (Box 93)
  - Welcome Week Class of 2021 Recording, Including Address by Former Dean of Admissions Shawn Abbott, 2017; cuid1738 (Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_RG_38-16-1-1_ER_1)
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009
  - 163rd NYU Commencement, 1995; 1 VHS (Box 16, Reel Project 74)
    Barcode: 31142042272891
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1995, 33 videocassettes (Box 27, Box 101)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1996; 20 videocassettes (Box 28)
  - Founder's Day, 1997; 1 Betamax (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272867
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 VHS (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 Betamax (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 videocassettes (Box 5, Reel Project 18)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 VHS (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - 165th NYU Commencement, 1997; 2 VHS
    - Original Recording, 2 VHS (Box 16, Reel Project 73)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:20)
  - Bagpipes for Commencement, 1997; 1 audiocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 77)
    Barcode: 31142042272941
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1997; 14 videocassettes (Box 29)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1997; 9 videocassettes (Box 30)
  - Grad Alley, 1998; 3 Betamax (Box 13, Reel Project 65)
  - 166th NYU Commencement: JumboTron, 1998; 1 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 66)
  - Founder's Day, 1998; 1 VHS (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272875
  - 166th NYU Commencement, 1998; 4 VHS (Box 16, Reel Project 66)
  - Stern Undergraduate Pre-commencement Footage, 1998; 1 VHS (Box 21, Reel Project 64)
  - NYU Grad Alley, 1998; 1 VHS (Box 19, Reel Project 65)
    Barcode: 31142042272925
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 23 videocassettes (Box 31)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 13 videocassettes (Box 32)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 9 videocassettes (Box 33)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 8 videocassettes (Box 34)
  - Founder's Day, 1999; 1 VHS (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 1999; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272883